Which are the news cities? How have these companies presented their results so far?
My colleague Arman has
joined us to discuss all this. And Honorable N,
first of all, tell us how have the numbers been after the market closed? These are the
companies' channels.
First of all, pay attention to ICC.
Lombard. If you look at their results, they are
better than what we had anticipated. Their net
premium end has increased by 18%.
If you look at their expense ratio, there has been a
decline in expansion as well.
From 30.7% to 28.8%, the combined
ratio, which we had estimated at 150%, has been reduced and has
increased to
105.1%. This is also
better than what we had anticipated. There has been an
increase of about 6.5% in revenue.
You will also see an increase of about 3% in dollar income and an
increase of about 3% in profit.
Along with this, if you look at the results in cash, the results for Flood
India have been good. They are about 18%
bigger. There has been a slight improvement in margins as well.
Anant Raj, the results have increased from 17.8% to 18.2%.
Here too the results are good, however,
you have seen a cut in the margins.
Although the income is 191% bigger and there is also a
128% increase in the profits, but if you
look at the margins, they have come down from 12.8% to 11.6%,
sorry, from 22.9% to 15.3%.
If you talk about Mahindra Automotive,
there too the income has increased by almost 30%. There are various
reasons for the margins being
cut from 12.8% to 11.6%. And if
you talk about Shelby,
if you look at the results there, the income is 11% bigger.
Margins have also seen an increase
from 16.2% to 18.3%. Along with that, a
72% increase was seen in the profits
of those companies which
released the numbers after the market closed yesterday. Armaan Nazar, tell me
what will be the important tricks for today,
where are those stock specific actions?
Results of big companies include
IndusInd Bank, Nestle and UltraTech Cement.
In F&O also, you will see results of seven to eight companies being reported, in
which these and
small finance banks Havells and Navin Fluorine are the
companies whose results will come.
Some changes are going to happen in Ascent indices too.
Aarti Industries will be removed from both SNB BSE 500 and SNB BSE 200.
Samvardhan
Madrasan Suny will be added to 500 and along with that
Adani Wilmar will also be added.
Our Prime Minister will inaugurate the Defence Expo today. Along with
that,
he is also going to launch Piramal
Pharma at the Deep Space Initiative in Gandhinagar, which is going to be listed there and that
platform will come for 10:10 trading. DC
Infotech and Communication, which will be
on board from such platform
in some stocks, including Technology
Intermediate 10 of 83 Industries, where the
allotment is one share, Aarti Pharmaceuticals will get
four shares in exchange of Bharti Industries.
Prestige State  If you talk about projects,
they have increased by 68%, whereas in H1, if you
look at the sales of the entire H1, you have
seen an increase of about 130%. Telecom
companies should pay attention to this because their
data has come in, in which if you talk about Reliance Jio,
they have added about 33 lakh customers,
Bharti Airtel has added about 3.6 lakh
customers and
if you look at Vodafone Idea, as usual, they have lost about 20 lakh
customers. ITC Limited
company, which is their mother Sparsh BV Care, has added
another 16% stake and now
their stake has increased to 22% there
and in exchange of these 1000 compulsory
convertible preference shares, they have made an MoU
with Bharat Electronics Limited India and this
MoU has been made for the needs of the Indian defense and export market, for the
possibilities,
and in this form there is the
production of the lake, in which Nomura India
bought it at a price of around 264